A Guide to the Clarence L. Townes Jr. Papers, 1944-1988
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series VI--Ephemera and photographs 1940s-1970s
  - A Friend is Someone Like You(inscribed On the Occasion of Your Birthday), Oversize (Box 30)
  - Planning book/calendar 1972, Oversize (Box 30)
  - GOP Planning book/calendar inscribed with Townes' name on cover 1970, Oversize (Box 30)
  - Photo/Poster of Clarence L. Townes, Jr. n.d., Oversize (Box 30)
  - From the Desk of Clarence L. Townes, Jr. Stationary, Oversize (Box 30)
  - Two different address/phone number rolodexes (Box 31)
  - Wooden plaque (Box 31)
  - Toy Beetle (Box 31)
  - Personal Motivation 45 RPM record by Paul J. Meyer, President, Success Motivation Institute, Inc. (Box 31)
  - Various hotel keys (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous political buttons (Box 32)
  - Ballard, Richard M.-National President of Phi Beta Sigma (Box 32)
  - Ballard, Richard M.; Vince Callahan; C.L. Townes; Unidentified man Campaign 1965 (Box 32)
  - Ballard, Richard M.; Vince Callahan; Winford Mundle; C.L. Townes; Arthur Brinkley, Mrs. Brinkley, Linwood Brown Camapaign 1965 (Box 32)
  - Black G.O.P. Committeemen, Chicago, Il 1970 (Box 32)
  - Broke, Sen. Edward, Mass 1968 (Box 32)
  - Callahan, Vince; C.L. Townes-Campaign 1965 (Box 32)
  - Callahan, Vince; C.L. Townes-Campaign 1965 (Box 32)
  - Dellums, Mrs. Ron (wife of congressman); C.L. Townes; Eddie Williams ca. 1973 (Box 32)
  - Ford, Gerald; Mr. Clay; Unidentified Congressman; C.L. Townes 1965 (Box 32)
  - Ford, Gerald; Alvin Dicer (sp); Mr. Clay; Unidentified Congressman; C.L. Townes 1965 (Box 32)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies-C.L. Townes; Mary McWherter, Unidentified Woman 1973 (Box 32)
  - Jones, Dr. Miles Richmond School Superintendent (Box 32)
  - King, Martin Luther; C.L. Townes (Box 32)
  - Larter, T. Milton; Mr. Humphries, C.L. Townes; Mary Gregory 1970s (Box 32)
  - Martin, Eddie (Box 32)
  - Nixon, Pres. Richard; George Lewis (GOP) 1969 (Box 32)
  - Nixon, Pres. Richard; C.L. Townes 1969 (Box 32)
  - Parker, Judge Barrington; Mrs. Parker, Mrs. Townes, C.L. Townes 1968 (Box 32)
  - Reagan, Ronald; C.L. Townes 1966 (Box 32)
  - Townes, C.L.-Campaign 1965 (Box 32)
  - Townes, C.L.; Mrs. Dorothy Monroe-Campaign 1965 (Box 32)
  - Townes, C.L.; Unidentified men, Republican Gala 1968 (Box 32)
  - Townes, C.L.-Various Promo. shots at RNC 1969 (Box 32)
  - Townes, C.L. 1960s (Box 32)
  - Townes, C.L. 1969 (Box 32)
  - Townes, C.L. 1966 (Box 32)
  - Townes, C.L. 1965 (Box 32)
  - Unidentified man, from GOP 1964 (Box 32)
  - White House meeting, President Nixon meets with black newspaper publishers 1969 (Box 32)
  - Williams, Eddie, Vernon Jordon, C.L. Townes Joint Center for Political Studies 1973 (Box 32)